<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<scripts>
    <script id="sob_open_1" newscaster="1">
        <line>BREAKING NEWS: Incident declared at prestigious university.</line>
        <line>The Westral Institute of Technology has declared an emergency after noticing that one of their prototypes has been stolen.</line> 
        <line>The university vice-chancellor, Daniel Ramston, urges anyone who thinks they know who stole the prototype to return it to their campus.</line> 
        <line>The prototype is believed to be a new autonomous car designed by Reina</line> 
        <line>that was going to be unveiled at the Technology Summit of the Atlantic North Nations (TSANN) next month in Everglade City at the Euclidean Expo Hall</line>
        <line>Organisers now say that the expo may be scaled back, or cancelled, due to security concerns.</line>
        <line>So far, the police have not made any arrests, but they currently believe a 26-year-old male called Harrison Felton might be responsible for the theft.</line> 
        <line>Felton is also wanted by Westral Police after attempting to rob the Bank of the Westral Federation in the Financial District of West Insbury.</line>
        <line>The public are being urged to exercise caution around him.</line>
    </script>
    <script id="sob_open_2" newscaster="2">
        <line>In other news, the government has announced that travel between Westeria and Saint Marys Islands will be restricted from tomorrow.</line>
        <line>The Temporary Travel Ban, or TTB, will come into effect at midnight, and it will infer a curfew, between 21:00, and 06:00.</line> 
        <line>During this curfew, citizens are reminded not to travel unless absolutely necessary.</line> 
        <line>Checkpoints are being installed on the Frank H. Beckett Bridge, and in the Mayrise Tunnel.</line> 
        <line>Roadblocks are being installed around Halifax Park, and West Insbury International Airport.</line> 
        <line>The Port of West Insbury will close to passenger traffic, and all rail travel between Saint Mary's and Westeria will be suspended.</line> 
        <line>The right to assembly will also be revoked.</line> 
        <line>Anyone on the streets after 9 pm, will be treated as potential hostiles.</line> 
        <line>The government is urging all citizens to remain indoors during the curfew.</line>

            <line>Many islands and human rights groups have voiced disapproval at the TTB, as the ban will mean that people cannot travel across the country, 
                but the government has listed people who are exempt from the ban. The islands of Allerton and Baxton are not under the ban.</line>
            <line>The Republic of Rey Del Sur has already announced that their embassy will close, until the TTB is lifted.</line> 
            <line>Similarly, the Northern Republic of Garcia has also announced that their embassy will remain closed indefinitely.</line>
            <line>Many other countries are relocating to non-restricted islands.</line> 
            <line>To view the full list, the government is urging people to go to www.gov.wf/travel-restriction/exceptions/.</line>
            </script>
    <script id="sob_open_3" newscaster="3">
            <line>The mayor of Allerton Bay has criticised the Westrian government for acting too harshly in response to a travel ban imposed today.</line> 
            <line>The ban, which came into force from yesterday, now means that most of the population is forbidden from travelling between islands via bridges, tunnels, ferries, railways and airports.</line>
            <line>Here is what the Mayor of Allerton Bay, Susan Keswick, had to say about the government's TTB:</line>
                <line speaker="susanKeswick">It is ridiculous! Why would you ban most of the country from travelling around, 
                    just because one person robbed from one of the most technologically advanced universities in the country, and attempted to rob one of the biggest banks in the country?</line> 
                    <line>We have gangs that are rife in the country, but nothing has been done about them!</line> 
                    <line>I have constituents who fear even stepping foot in some districts!!</line>
                    <line>I know that gangs are rife in West Insbury, but I do not see Westral Police paying any attention to them at all!</line> 
                    <line>I've seen drug deals openly happening on the streets, with NO police in sight!</line>
                    <line>We are supposed to be protected by the police, but this is too far in terms of protecting the country! I dare say this may be borderline mollycoddling.</line>

                <line>In response to the comments made by mayor Keswick, the commissioner of Westral Police issued a statement on the situation:</line>

                <line speaker="markRowley">Due to the security risk to the citizens of the Westral Federation, The government was advised to lock down travel between the islands, until police can identify what happened.</line> 
                <line>While I can understand the comments made by Miss Keswick, I would like to remind Miss Keswick that her town falls outside of the TTB, and people are able to freely travel around the islands of Allerton and Baxton.</line> 
                <line>The TTB only applies to Westeria and Saint Mary's, however, there is a country-wide ban on domestic travel from air and sea.</line> 
                <line>Airports and ports across the Westral Federation will remain open throughout the TTB, but no domestic flights or ferries will be running.</line> 
                <line>Rail services will continue to run across the rest of the country, except for between West Insbury, and Saint Mary's or West Insbury and Haddock Bay.</line>
    </script>
</scripts>